folica.com 2016-06-25

# Folica.com - The best selection of hair care, flat irons and hair styling products anywhere

### Last Updated 01-06-2014

Folica, Inc. ("Folica") owns and operates this web site, Folica.com ("Web Site"). Folica recognizes and respects the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers, registered members ("Members") and users, and has established this Privacy Policy as a result. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of: the personal information we may collect from you when you visit our Web Site, respond to our emails, place orders via mail or fax, or otherwise contact us via telephone, email, fax or mail.

Note: You must be 18 years or older to use, subscribe or register as a member of Folica.com. The Web Site is a general audience site and we do not knowingly collect, maintain or disclose personal information from or about children under the age of 13. If Folica becomes aware that a child under 13 has provided personally identifiable information, we will take reasonable steps to remove such information and terminate the respective account.

### Why do we gather information?

Folica.com gathers personal information to help improve our products and customer service, to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide you with an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience, and to inform you of special offers and discounts from us and selected third parties.

### What information do we gather?

We collect information through our Web Site, emails, mail, fax, and telephone, including when you:

  * place an order,
  * participate in our forums, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, promotions, content submissions, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups, requests for suggestions, and membership registrations, and
  * engage in other activities, services, products and resources we make accessible to our customers, members or users.

Depending on how you interact with us, we collect some or all of the following types of information:

  * your name, address, telephone number, email address,
  * billing information (credit/debit card number, expiration date, alternate or additional billing information and billing address),
  * gender and birth date, if you choose, or are otherwise required to, enter such information,
  * products purchased
  * any promotion or gift card code and related information, and
  * other information you provide to us.
  * Information shared via your social media account. (see Social Media section)

Information you provide may be collected by us even if an order, registration, or other process is started but not completed or otherwise cancelled. Members may also add to their Address Book the name, address and telephone number of friends or other persons to whom they may wish to send orders. Other Members do not have the right to view and edit your Address Book entries.

Upon completing a purchase with Folica, a customer is automatically opted in for e-mails. To opt out, please e-mail: unsubscribe@folica.com.

When you use the Ratings & Reviews or the Question & Answer services you will become a registered user (if you aren’t already one) and any personal information you submit will become part of your profile, as maintained by Folica.

### Social Media

Folica invites you to socialize and share your hair care finds and purchases with your friends using Social Media tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Instagram. If you choose to use these tools, you may be sharing certain profile elements, including your comments. This sharing is subject to each social media program's privacy policies. We also use Facebook Social Plugins to allow Facebook to share information and friends' activities with its members while they are on our website. For example, Social Plugins allow Facebook to show you and your friends' "Likes" on our product pages if you are logged into Facebook while shopping at Folica com. Folica does not receive or control any of the content from Facebook Social Plugins. For more information about Facebook Social Plugins and other social media tools, click this [link](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/). 

We may allow you to sign in to your Folica.com account using your social media account. If you choose to do this, we may collect information necessary to facilitate social interactions such as friend lists, birthday, check-ins, basic profile information and your profile picture but only if the privacy settings you and your friends set within your account allow it. We will use the information we collect to create and facilitate an interactive social experience and to bring you products, services and programs from Folica.com . Folica.com will always comply both with its privacy policy as well as with terms and conditions regarding use of your social media profile information. 

### How we use "Cookies" and "Action Tags".

A "cookie" is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer, user or Member and to provide certain features to you. Most web browsers allow you to instruct the browser to prevent the use of cookies. However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of Folica.com Web Site, such as the cart, may not function properly.

We have relationships with third parties who may receive non-personal information directly from the cookies placed by our Web Site on your computer to assist in analyzing our business and customers.

Our Web Site also uses a common web technology called "action tags" (also called single pixel gifs or web beacons) to anonymously track purchase, usage and other web activity information. Action tags (including third party tags) may be used to provide data to third parties for tracking purposes. However, our Web Site does not currently use action tags to collect or transfer personal information.

### Interest-based advertising

### Other websites

Advertisements for our products and services may appear on third party websites around the Internet. Some websites and services deliver these advertisements based upon data that has been previously collected about your past behavior online. For example, if you have viewed websites about hair care, these websites or services may display to you an advertisement for our hair care products. This kind of targeted advertising is sometimes called interest-based or online behavioral advertising. It is generally not based upon your personal information, but rather, upon your online activities.

We do not control such third party websites or services on which these advertisements appear. Further, we do not control how they collect and use data about your online activities. However, you may opt-out of being tracked online by certain companies by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. If you opt-out, you will still receive advertisements, but they will not be delivered to you based upon your behavioral data possessed by the companies from whom you have opted-out. This process relies upon an opt-out cookie, so if you delete your cookies or use a different computer, you will have to repeat this process.

### Our Web Site

In addition, from time-to-time, our Web Site may also carry advertisements from other companies. Some of these advertisements may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based, for example, on commercial interests you have expressed during your online activities. You may opt-out of receiving this type of targeted advertising by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp to learn more about online behavioral advertising and how to opt-out from interest-based advertising ads served by some or all participating companies. Once again, if you opt-out, you will still receive advertisements, but they will not be delivered to you based upon your behavioral data possessed by the companies from whom you have opted-out. This process relies upon an opt-out cookie, so if you delete your cookies or use a different computer, you will have to repeat this process.

### How we use the information we collect

We use information we collect to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide you with an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience, to inform you and of offers and discounts from Folica.com, and to enable you to receive credits for purchases under loyalty or buying programs which you have joined. We may engage email and other service providers in connection with the foregoing, and you consent to having the information we collect transferred to them for that purpose. Our service providers have agreed to treat such information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. In addition, we may make such information (except for credit/debit card number and expiration date, unless you consent otherwise), including aggregated information, available to selected third parties including, but not limited to, those who share or rent information for direct marketing purposes.

Otherwise, without your consent, we do not make your email addresses, available to "third parties" (as that term is defined and limited below). For example, we may make your postal address available to third parties for marketing purposes; however, we would not share your email address without your consent. In addition, you may instruct that other personal information about you to us not be shared with third parties by following the instructions in How to Limit the Use of Personal Information, below.

Our Affiliates, subcontractors, service providers and agents, and any successors or assignees to our business (if we ever sell, lease, license or assign some or all of our business), are not considered to be third parties under this Privacy Policy. We may provide your information to our Affiliates for use in connection with their businesses, including sending you offers and promotions. However, in connection with information collected under this Privacy Policy, they are required to comply with this Privacy Policy. "Affiliates" are persons or entities directly or indirectly controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Folica.com

We may combine information we receive from you via our Web Site, emails, mail, fax, and telephone with information from our Affiliates and third parties. We use the combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us and to communicate with you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to disclose information you provide to us as required by law, in response to legal process and law enforcement requests and as necessary or appropriate, in our view, to operate the Web Site, process orders or registrations, to conduct promotions, contests, and sweepstakes you participate in, and to protect the rights or property of the Company, its Affiliates, users, customers, recipients, Members, Sponsors, Providers, Licensors, Merchants and Associates.

Please note that all information (including personal information) that you reveal or post on one of our public forums such as a message board, chat room, discussion group, folder, survey, contest, sweepstakes, user review and rate forum, and all User Submissions, are not protected by this Privacy Policy and may be collected, shared and used by us (and third parties) without restriction or your permission. Information you give out or post on our public forums is disclosed at your own risk.

Folica may also transfer any and all information it collects for the Web Site (including personal information, registration data, e-mail addresses, purchase histories, traffic data and information from public forums) to any successor to all or substantially all of its business or assets related to the Web Site.

### Consent to Transfer and Submission

Folica.com is operated in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to and stored in the United States. By using the Web Site or otherwise providing us with information, you hereby consent to this transfer.

Although personal information collected by us through the Web Site, emails, mail, fax, and telephone is used by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy, laws generally applicable to the protection of personal data in the U.S. may not be as stringent as those in other countries.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Folica.com wants you to be aware that when you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to affiliated or third-party web sites, you will be subject to the privacy policies and terms of use of those web sites, not ours. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms whenever using, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other web site.

### Security and Passwords

If you place an order on our Web site, we encrypt the credit/debit card number you submit prior to transmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology. This technology works best when the Web Site is viewed using Microsoft Internet Explorer®, Google Chrome®, Mozilla Firefox®, and Apple Safari® browsers. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we make reasonable efforts to safeguard personal information once we receive it (including by complying with all Payment Card Industry (PCI) security requirements, we cannot guarantee the security of information we receive.

Portions of the Web Site (such as our Member registration) may require registration and log-in processes in which you will select a user ID and password (collectively, the "Password"). Passwords provided to you by us are the confidential property of the Company and may be used by you solely for your individual use of the Web Site (and otherwise as specified by us). You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any Password and for all activities that occur using your Password, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your Password or accounts. Passwords are encrypted and cannot be decrypted by Folica but only reset. Folica will never ask you divulge your password.

We may provide you with the ability to log into our service using a social media account, such as Facebook Connect. We do not control the activities of such social media services and have no control over the data they collect or their privacy practices. You should review their privacy practices before using any such social media service. Even if you access our Web Site using a social media account, this Privacy Policy shall apply to your use of our service and Web Site.

By identifying yourself through a social media account, Folica may obtain additional information about your corresponding profile (to the extent permitted by the terms, conditions and functions of that social media service).

### How to Limit the Use of Personal Information

We want to communicate with you only to the extent you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to have personal information collected from you via the Web Site, emails, mail, fax, and telephone shared with third parties, or to set your preferences concerning promotional communications, please follow the directions below.

### From Third Parties

We do not share email addresses you provide with third parties without your consent. In addition, if you prefer that other personal information provided by you not be shared with third parties, please let us know by emailing, writing or calling us as described below. Your instructions will be processed as soon as reasonably practicable and in accordance with law.

Emailing us at: unsubscribe@folica com from the email address which you wish to have removed (i.e. not shared with third parties), and include your postal mailing address in the message; or

Writing us at:

Customer Service Department

Inventory Receiving/Returns:   
Folica, Inc.  
11 Corn Road, Suite B   
South Brunswick, NJ 08810 

Telephoning us at 1-888-919-4247

### From our Affiliates

If you also prefer not to have us provide personal information about you to our Affiliates, please indicate in your email or letter that you wish your instructions to apply to our "Affiliates."

### Corrections

If you would like to update or correct information previously provided to us, please send an e-mail with your new information, including your complete name, postal address, and email address to fcs@folica.com.

Members can modify and update their membership information (including name, mailing address, birth date, telephone number and email address) by accessing the password-protected "Your account page" page.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Your Consent and Changes to this Policy

Subject to the above provisions, by using our Web Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time as new features or services are added, suggestions from our customers are incorporated or other changes are made.

The date on which the current Privacy Policy took effect is listed at the top of the Privacy Policy.

By using folica.com after such changes take effect, you agree to be legally bound and to abide by the revised Privacy Policy.

### Your Comments

Folica.com wants to hear your feedback concerning this policy. Please send your comments and questions to fcs@folica.com or by writing us at:

Customer Service Department

Inventory Receiving/Returns:   
Folica, Inc.  
11 Corn Road, Suite B   
South Brunswick, NJ 08810 

### Notification of Changes

Folica reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
